## **Business Center Manager III**

# ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

## **Objective**

Dynamic, energetic professional seeking to secure an mid-level position with a growing company that offers opportunity for career advancement. 10-12 years Experience in Administration Management, Management operations, and customer service. Trained in Firefighting, Damage Control, Safety, Hazmat, EMT.

#### Skills

Microsoft Office, Customer Relationship Management, Leadership Development, Problem Resolution, Kronos, SAP.

## **Work Experience**

#### **Business Center Manager III**

ABC Corporation - March 2011 - July 2016

- Use computers for various applications, such as database management or word processing.
- Perform payroll functions, such as maintaining timekeeping information and processing and submitting payroll.
- Collect and deposit money into accounts, disburse funds from cash accounts to pay bills or invoices, keep records of collections and disbursements, and ensure accounts are balanced.
- Create, maintain, and enter information into databases.
- Set up and manage paper or electronic filing systems, recording information, updating paperwork, or maintaining documents, such as attendance records, correspondence, or other material.
- Operate office equipment, such as fax machines, copiers, or phone systems and arrange for repairs when equipment malfunctions.
- Analyze operations to evaluate performance of center or staff in meeting objectives or to determine areas of potential cost reduction, program improvement, or policy change.

## **Business Center Manager**

**Delta Corporation** - 2009 - 2011

- Drive revenue for center by meeting with new customers, monitor and direct marketing activities for center to accomplish sales objectives Hire team .
- Responsible for manufacturing processes for critical plant systems.
- Controlled projects, estimated production cost, managed raw materials and oversaw operations.
- Authored universal Policy and Procedure manual(s) for all Xerox Business Centers located in Disney as well as local area off-property hotels.
- Provided equipment and support for entire American Medical Association at WDW Swan hotel during 2001 Annual International Medical Conference.
- Provided outstanding equipment, product and service to WDW Swan and Dolphin Hotels as well as Hyatt Regency Grand Cypress hotel from 2000 to 2001.
- · Hired and trained the assistant managers.

#### **Education**

A.A in Political Science - (Copper Mountain College)	